<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Project</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="triund">The trek to Triund was my first trek ever in Himachal Pradesh. It is very much near to my hometown. Triund is also a basic trek. It is not that hard to scale it. Triund  trek can be described as a tranquil trek which can be easily accomplished by almost all age groups. This trek can be accomplished by two ways. One is from Dharamkot, Which I think is 2 Km form MacLeodganj. The trek starts from Galu temple, Dharamkot and you have to travel around 7 Km to reach to Triund. If you have a large group of friends then you can choose this side because the other way is via bhagsunag waterfall and Shiva cafe which can be quite challenging for some of your friends who are not familiar with trekking. One can choose this way on returning back. I would suggest to start your trek from Dharamkot which goes through the Oak and Rhododendron forest. It will be quite refreshing to walk among the forest and share the moment with your friends or family. And you can return from the other way which will give you a scenic view of Kangra valley. It is very much recharging and exhilarating when you are tired of all the trek. The trek is quite interesting and full of adventurous events. There are a lot of Tea shops in the way for refreshment. you can also ask them for the tea which is made of goat\'s milk. The trek is easy for 5 en dash 6 Km. The hard part is after snowline cafe, which is a steep climb of about 1 Km. It is also known as \'22 curves\' because in this part you have to face 22 steep curves which are quite exhausting and mentally breaking. After all this hectic trek there comes Triund with an majestic view of Himalayas overseeing the whole valley.  You can also see HPCA, Dharamshala from there. Triund is also the base camp for Inderhara trek in Dhauladhar ranges. On the way to Inderhara pass, there are a lot of \'Lungru\' plants\(you know if you are a Himachali\) and for those who don\'t know it is a kind of vegetable which is eaten in Himachal with a great liking for it. I have also collected some lungru for my home on my way back. It was a sort of experience which has encouraged me to explore every side of Himalayas. I would like to recommend this trek for those who are beginners. Atlast, I would like to say Please don\'t litter Himalayas.</string>
    <string name="dhankar">Dhankar Lake was the most beautiful trek that I and my travelling partner, Pranav Thakur, did last year in June, 2018. And I think it\'s the best time to go to Spiti valley.  It is also known as Sarkund. It is approached from Dhankar village. we reached the base of Dhankar Lake at around 4:00 PM after visiting Dhankar Village which is also very scenic in it\'s own way which is a different story. I will surely write about Dhankar village some other day. Now talking about Dhankar Lake which is situated above the village Dhankar at an elevation of approximately 4100 meters in the middle of the hills. Actually this lake was in our itinerary and pre en dash planned that we will visit their afternoon because at that time sun will be less aggressive. but instead of this we had to wear our sun screen\(It should be at least SPF 50\). The trek was only of around 2 Hours. The first hour, it was nice and easy. The hill was cooperating with us. And the next hour was very rough on us. The hill we were walking on had loose pebbles that we could slip from their  and reach the bottom of it in no time. Though it was quite risky but we carved out our way through it. We met a lot of people in our way to the lake. The most interesting thing about them is they all would tell you some different timings to reach the top and at the  same time they are quite encouraging. As we were walking up on the ridge thinking that this is the last ridge and you would reach your spot but as usual, we had few more steep ridges to cross over. We kept moving and taking alternative rest throughout the way. We also had some refreshments with us. After crossing consecutive steep ridges we landed up in a barren land accompanied by thorny bushes. There we asked a local native of that village,\"Bhai, Aur kitni door hai?\" and he replied, \"Bus aap log pahunch hee gaye\". Today also I remembered those words. You could ask anything from the locals, they are very helping and caring. After taking few more steps and we reached our much predicted lake! It is a huge water body which spreads over a large area and the water is as clear as a day. One can also do camping up here. There is a lot of space around this lake. We both sat on the banks of the lake silently without blinking our eyes for minutes. We were continuously gazing at the lake and adoring it\'s beauty in our mind. The mixture of barren hills and green lake was mesmerizing. The happening of this beautiful lake upon the hills is not less than a miracle. The lake looks like if we were in heaven. Is gives a spiritual feeling that Gods must be living somewhere here. After some time we walked around the lake and took every shot possible till the battery of the camera died. Instead of covering each and every part you know your soul will always be thirsty and unsatisfied of such enchanting views. It\'s too much windy on the banks of lake. There is also small temple beside this lake. The lake has it\'s own beautiful texture. Sometimes it will be green and at the same time it is crystal clear. And I have read somewhere that the lake is fish shaped and it is shaped like the way! I will come here again soon because this lake has made a separate place in my heart. At last, I must say whenever you go for trekking, it\'s best to have a travelling partner  always. Please! By littering mountains don\'t destroy their beauty!
Keep Himalayas plastic free.</string>
    <string name="chandarshila">On your trek to the summit, you will witness some of the finest views of the snow cladded mountain ranges, white clouds and dense forests.

Notably, the Chopta Chandrashila trek is a steep ascent of over 1300 m. It is neither a lengthy nor a difficult trek. From Chopta, it only takes around 2 en dash 3 hours to reach Tungnath. The journey of steep climbing begins at the last 1.5 km from the temple towards Chandrashila, which means the trekking is quite easy and comfortable.

Sure, it\’s no a walk in the park, but even someone of an average fitness can easily make it. No wonder, for many, this trek marks their Himalayan debut. The trek trail is well laid out till Tungnath, the highest Shiva temple in the world. It’s not flat, but a steady uphill climb. The trail is well defined and there is no chance of getting lost even if you are alone.

The trail to Chandrashila from here is hardly 1.5 kms in length, maintaining a slow and steady pace to reach the top. The summit has a small temple and a series of cairns. Once at the top, the nature\’s canvas to unfurl in front of your eyes.</string>
    <string name="kareri">On the way to the lake, you will witness the best views the nature has to offer with lush green and dense forests. You will easily spot a lot of exotic birds on your way.

It is a lengthy and a tiring trek but not difficult. Beware of your surroundings, the probability of finding a bear (Reech in the native language) on this trek is way more than any of the others. The trek is full of ups and downs which will surely exhaust you but one can can find a lot of fresh water sources to keep himself hydrated.

After around 3 hours of trek you will reach a place called Reoti, where you can find a couple of small tea shops to refresh yourself and rest for a while. The prices here are less than that of Triund but still overpriced. The place is best recognized by the beautiful footbridge across the Nyund stream.

From Reoti the lake is another 5 km. The trail is well defined covered with rhododendrons, oaks and deodars. After a tiring climb, you will walk the lasts step across the Nyund stream without a bridge for a final climb for Kareri Lake and will enter the high shores of the lake.
    Campsite:
    Once you have reached the top, you will experience one of the best views of the Dhauladhar valley. You will find one seasonal tea shop, some camping tents, 6 en dash 8 seasonal Gaddi Huts and a temple dedicate to Lord Shiva. Here you will also get to witness the Minkiani Pass \(4250m\) in the background of the freshwater lake.
        Once at the campsite, you can either use your own or rent a tent from any of the shops along the way which will cost you around ₹400 for two after a good bargain.</string>
</resources>
